{
  "questions": [ 
       {
           "question": "jQuery is free and open source.",
           "answers": ["True", "False"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 1
       },
       {
           "question": "Which of the following type of variable is visible everywhere in your JavaScript code?",
           "answers": ["global variable", "local variable","Both of the above","None of the above"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 1
       },
       {
           "question": "Which built-in method combines the text of two strings and returns a new string?",
           "answers": ["append()", "concat()", "attach()", "None of the above."],
       	   "correctAnswer": 2
       },
       {
           "question": "Which of the following function of Array object sorts the elements of an array?",
           "answers": ["toSource()", "sort()", "toString()", "unshift()"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 2
       },
       {
           "question": "What is JSON?",
           "answers": ["Java Script Object Native", "Java Script Oriented Notation","Java Script Object Notation","None"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 3
       },
       {
           "question": "Java Source Code is compiled into?",
           "answers": ["Source Code", ".obj", ".exe", "Bytecode"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 4
       },
       {
           "question": "Single line comment starts with _________ in Java.",
           "answers": ["/**", "/*", "//", "None"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 3
       },
       {
           "question": "Which of the following primitive types can only have two possible values?",
           "answers": ["byte", "char", "boolean", "short"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 3
       },
       {
           "question": "Which of the following is not a keyword in Java.?",
           "answers": ["boolean", "finalize", "assests", "abstract"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 2
       },
       {
           "question": "Which of the following ends an infinite for loop?",
           "answers": ["stop();", "end;", "break;", "exit();"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 3
       },
       {
           "question": "this keyword in java is used to ?",
           "answers": ["refer to current class object.", "refer to static method of the class.", "refer to parent class object.", "refer to static variable of the class."],
       	   "correctAnswer": 1
       },
       {
           "question": "Can you make Constructor Final?",
           "answers": ["Yes", "No"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 2
       },
       {
           "question": "Which of the following supports the concept of hierarchical classification?",
           "answers": ["Polymorphism", "Encapsulation", "Abstraction", "Inheritance"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 4
       },
       {
           "question": "Which Keyword from the following is used to inherit properties from one class into another?",
           "answers": ["extends", "subclasses", "native", "all of the mentioned"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 1
       },
       {
        "question": "Which of the following concept is often expressed by the phrase, ‘One interface, multiple methods’?",
        "answers": ["Abstraction", "Polymorphism", "Inheritance", "Encapsulation"],
           "correctAnswer": 2
        }
     ]
 }
